敵だ！
It's the enemy!
来たぞ！！
They're coming!
（シカマル）まったく…
これじゃ　キリがねえぜ。
Damn it, there's no end to them.
ただ　ただ消耗していく…
いつまで続くんだ？
They're just wearing us out.
How long is this going
to continue?
うん？　雨…。
Rain?
天気雨…。
It's raining while sunny?
≪別方向から敵！！
The enemy is coming from
a different direction!
《白いのとは違う。
アイツも穢土転生？》
He's not one of those white guys...
Was he reanimated too?
Is he crying?
泣いてる？
He looks like a child.
子供にも見えるが…
チッ…　戦争ってやつかよ！
But this is a war, after all!
なんだ…　この雨は…。
What's with this rain?
くっ…　うっ…。
（スクイ）サクラ！　入るわよ。
I'm coming in, Sakura!
（サクラ）はい。
Okay!
そこの台にお願いします。
（スクイ）よろしく。
Place him on that table!
Take care of this.
（スクイ）次！
はい！
– We're moving on to the next one!
– Okay!
（サクラ）あなた…　誰？
Who are you?
フフフ…　フフフフフ…。
なに？
What's going on?
雪？
Snow?
Hey... What are you doing?
ちょ…　何してんの！
♪♪「コン　コン　コン　雪だコン
コン　コン　コン　雪だコン」
Kon, kon, kon...
It's snowing, kon...
It's snowing, kon.
Kon, kon, kon...
えっ…　えっ…。
Huh?
What?!
（サクラ）え～っ！？
うっ…。
（シノ）蟲玉！
Beetle Sphere!
（キバ）牙通牙！
Fang Over Fang!
（キバ）赤丸！
（赤丸）ワン　ワン！
Akamaru!
クソ…　雷遁か？
Damn it! Lightning Style, huh?!
ワン！　ワン　ワン！
（キバ）誰かいる。
Someone's there!
ワン　ワン！　ワン　ワン！
お前　知ってるのか？
Do you know who it is?
プン　プン　プン…。
プン　プン　プン！
怒ってるのか？
ワン　ワン！
Is he angry?
うわっ！！
（ナルト）みんな…　待ってろよ。
Hold on, everyone!
Rain Followed by Snow,
with Some Lightning
（チョウザ）なんだ？　あの雨。
What was that rain?
（ダルイ）新手の敵っすかね？
だるいっす。
Do you think it's a new enemy?
How tiresome...
（シカマル）くっ！
うぅ…。
（チョウジ）倍化の術！
Expansion Jutsu!
チョウジ！
（いの）シカマル！
Choji!
Shikamaru!
すまねえ　いの…。
Sorry, Ino!
影首縛りの術！
Shadow Strangle Jutsu!
成功。
Complete!
（３人）うわ～！
縛ってんのに　どうして　術を！？
How can he still use jutsu
while he's bound?
（いの）ちょ…　これって！
Hey... This is...
くっ！　印が…。
My sign!
What's with this rain?
なんなの！？　この雨！
あぁ…。
（チョウジ）動けない…。
I can't move.
Damn it.
クソ！
シカマル！　チョウジ！　いの！
Shikamaru, Choji, Ino...
It's me!
私だよ。
コイツ…　なんで　私たちの名前を？
How does he know our names?!
僕　知らないよ　こんなヤツ。
I don't know him.
Me neither.
俺もだよ。　うっ！
What?!
なっ！
イタッ！
うわっ！
Ouch!
雪だ　コン！
えっ？
It's snowing, kon.
What?
Ouch!
イテッ！
お前…。
You're...
アンタ！
そうか！
ワン　ワン！
I remember...
ヨタ！
（２人）ヨタ！
Yota!
– Yota!
ヨタ！
Yota!
《シカマル：ヨタ…　そうだ！
俺たちは　お前を知っている》
Yota...
That's right... We know you.
((ここらへんだと思うんだけど。
I think it's around here.
大事なクナイのセットなのに…
どうしよう？
It's a precious kunai set.
What'll I do?
クナイなんて　投げるもんなんだから
なくなんのは　しかたねえだろ？
Kunai are meant for throwing,
so it can't be helped
if you lose them.
But my mom bought them for me
だって　あれは
アカデミーに入った記念に→
as a reward for getting into
the Academy!
母ちゃんに買ってもらったんだよ。
なくしちゃったら
母ちゃんが悲しむよ…。
If I lose them,
my mom's going to be sad.
チョウジは優しい子なんだから
つきあってあげるの！
Choji is a nice kid,
so we're going to help him out.
はぁ…　面倒くせぇな。
What a pain.
僕のクナイ…。
My kunai.
Damn it,
where did you throw them?
ったく…　どこへ投げたんだよ？
ないわね…。
I can't find it.
あっ！
雨…。
Huh?
Rain...
あれ！？　おかしいな？
Huh? That's odd.
天気なのに…。
It's sunny too.
ん！？
な…　なんだ！？　ありゃ！
何？
W-What is that?!
What?
えっ！？　ちょ…　あれ　人？
Hey...
Is that a person?
Oh!
あ～っ！
My kunai!
僕のクナイだ！
なんだよ？　アイツ…。
僕のクナイが刺さってるよ。
What's wrong with him?
My kunai are stuck on him!
How did it get there?!
どうやったら　あんなとこに…。
Anyway, let's go.
とにかく　行こうぜ！
うん！
Yeah.
僕のクナイ！
My kunai!
情けないわね！
How pathetic.
I still haven't learned
the Tree Climbing Jutsu yet,
木登りの術なんて
まだ　教わってねえよ…。
親父たちみたいに
スタコラ登れるかっての！
so I can't climb it
as easily as our dads.
でも…　大事なクナイが！
But my precious kunai!
（チョウジ／シカマル）あぁ～！
キャーッ！
Damn it.
クソーッ！
うわ～っ！
シカマル　チョウジ！
Shikamaru! Choji!
Hey, wait.
え　ちょ　ちょっと　うわ～っ！
Choji!
チョウジ！
（ヨタ）ぴったんこ　アハッ！
Good-good!
Huh?
アハハハッ…。
アハハハハッ…。
雨が…。
やんだ。
The rain...
It stopped.
（チョウジ／ヨタ）アハハハハッ。
WEATHER FOR SALE
(ん？))
You're Yota, aren't you?
ヨタなんだろ　お前。
ヨタ　思い出した。
Yota... I remember!
That's right...
How could we forget!
そうだよ　なんで　今まで…。
ヨタ　お前も穢土転生。
えっ？
Yota... You're a Reanimation...
コイツも…。
What?
Him too?
（３人）うわ～っ！
そうだ　ヨタは天気を操ることが。
That's right...
Yota can control the weather.
ヨタ　やめてくれよ！
Yota... Please stop!
うわ～っ！
ヨタの意思じゃねえよ。
ヨタは　操られて。
Yota's not doing it on purpose.
He's being controlled.
じゃあ　ヨタはもう…。
Then that means that
Yota is already...
((私　ヨタ。
ヨタ？
Me... Yota.
Yota? Is that your name?
名前？
うん！
Yeah.
私って　女かよ。
男だよ。
You're a girl?
I'm a boy.
男で　私かよ。
そうだよ　私は私。
You're a boy who talks like a girl?
That's right. I'm me.
お前　木ノ葉のもんじゃないよな。
You're not from the Leaf are you?
私　違うよ。
どっから来たの？
I'm different.
Where did you come from?
ん？　いろいろなところから。
From all over the place.
いろいろって　国は？
ない。
From all over?
What nation are you from?
Nowhere.
里は？
ないよ。
What village?
I don't have one.
アハハハッ　ないよ　ないない！
I have none, none, none.
ウフフフッ　アハハハッ。
ひとりぼっちなのかな？
どうやら　そうみてえだな。
I wonder if he's lonely.
It sure seems like it.
どうする？
里の大人たちに知らせたほうが。
What should we do?
We should let the adults
in the village know.
ダメだよ。
え？
We can't.
知らない人が入り込んで
この前だって→
There was a big fuss
not too long ago
大騒ぎしたじゃないか。
about a stranger coming in.
今は　里と里が
すごいピチピチしてるって→
My dad said that there's big-big
trouble between the villages.
父ちゃんが言ってた。　だから…。
そうだよな。　ヨタみてえなヤツが
今　里に現れたら。
That's right.
If someone like Yota
showed up in the village...
– Hmm...
ピチピチ　ヒャハハハ。
Big-big.
あ？
ピチピチ。　フハハハ。
Big-big.
チョウジは　ピチピチしてるね。
You're pretty big-big, huh, Choji?
え！？
Huh?
ピチピチというより　ポッチャリかな？
I'm not really big,
but just chubby.
デブデブしてる。
You're a fatty-fatso.
ぼ…　ぼ…　僕は→
I-I'm...n-not a fatso!
デ…　デ…　デブじゃな～い！
まずい！
This is bad!
ん～！
フハ　フハハハハ。
待て！
Come back!
この！
Why you...
ヨタ？　どうしたの？
Yota?
What's wrong?
私のお腹　スカスカ…。
My stomach is empty-empty.
お腹？　ハハハ…。
ハハハ。
Stomach?
へへっ　うまそうに食べてやがる。
He looks like he's enjoying it.
うん！
うらやましい。
Yeah.
I'm so jealous.
もっと。
もう　ねえよ。
More!
There isn't anymore.
贅沢だよ　ヨタ。
You're asking too much of us, Yota.
私　お腹減ってる。
グウグウする。　もっと　もっと！
I'm starving.
It's growling. More, more.
無理言わないの！
Don't ask the impossible.
もういっちょ　もういっちょ
もういっちょ！
One more, one more, one more!
しつこい！
Stop that!
うわぁ～ん。
泣かないの！
Don't cry!
うわぁ～　あぁ～。
ええ！？
また　天気雨。
It's raining again while sunny.
待てよ　さっきもヨタが泣いて…。
Wait... Yota was crying earlier too.
もう泣かない！
Hey! Stop crying!
いのがいじめる。
うわ！
Ino is picking on me...
ヨタが泣くから　雨が降ってるのか？
It's raining because
Yota is crying...
グスッ　わかるよ。
I understand.
僕　ポッチャリ系だから
ヨタの気持　すっごくわかる。
I'm chubby, so I really understand
how Yota feels.
僕まで　お腹減った。
I'm feeling hungry too.
ごめんね　ヨタ。
私が言いすぎた。
Sorry, Yota. I went too far.
どうなってんだ。
なんでお前らまで？
What's going on?
Why are you guys crying too?
悲しくねえのに　悲しいんだ。
I'm not even sad.
But I feel sad.
(ヨタから　もらい泣きかよ))
We caught the crying from Yota?
ヨタ。
Yota...
ヨタ…。
ヨタ！　僕たちは
お前と戦いたくなんかないんだよ。
Yota... We don't want to fight you!
アンタもそうなんでしょ？
You don't want to
fight either, right?
きっとそうだよ　ヨタだもん。
I'm sure that he doesn't.
It's Yota!
わかってんだろ
こいつはヨタの意思なんかじゃねえ。
Don't you understand?
Yota isn't in control here.
アスマのときと同じだ。
It's the same thing,
like what happened with Asuma!
穢土転生…　くそっ！
Damn Reanimation Jutsu!
ヨタ！
Yota...
（サクラ）ヨタ！
デコ！
Yota!
Forehead!
ヘヘヘッ！
ヨタ…。
♪♪「コン　コン　コン　雪だコン
コン　コン　コン　雪だコン」
また雪？
♪♪「コン　コン　コン　雪だコン
コン　コン　コン　雪だコン」
♪♪「コン　コン　コン　雪だコン」
ヨタ…。
楽しいんだね。
♪♪「コン　コン　コン」
((ヨタ？
ヨタ！
あっ！
（シカマル）ヨタ！
（チョウジ）僕たちだよ。
寝てたら起きて！
（３人）ヨタ！
シカマル　チョウジ　いの！
んっ　ん～　デコ！
えっ！？　わっ…　わっ　あぁ！
あっ　オメエは！
あっ…　あっ！
イタタ…。
サクラ！
あっ…　あっ！
デコ！
えっ？
キャハ！　アハハハハ！　ハハハハ！
雪？
(晴れてるのに…。
天気…　雪？))
♪♪「コン　コン　コン　雪だコン」
うっ…。
♪♪「コン　コン　コン　雪やコン
コン　コン　コン　雪やコン」
ヨタ…。
うわぁ～ん！
（キバ）ヨタ！
あれは…。
皆様　お変わりございませんか？
美空ひばりです。
では最後まで　ごゆっくり→
お楽しみください。
（宮本）『木曜８時のコンサート
名曲！にっぽんの歌』。
（松丸）今回は　ご覧の豪華な歌手
１１組の皆さんによる→
華麗なステージをお届けいたします。
皆さんどうぞ
よろしくお願いいたします。